Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. 2002 Accrual, 1894-1997; 354 Linear feet in 147 boxes.
  - Subseries VI.F. Rolled Drawings, 1936-1993; 291 Linear feet in 83 boxes.
    - 86-2148 | C. S. H. Beach Club (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 86-2148 | C. S. H. Bead Club Sire Dwg. (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 86-2150 | Tom Pulling (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 86-2151 | R. Powers (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2153 | McLaughlin (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 86-2158 | Krais (Gordon) (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2161 | B. Hansen (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2163 | P. Huntington (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-[unknown job number] | Post Lot 6 Cold Springs Harbor (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 87-2169 | David O'Neill (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 87-2170 | Finkel (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-550)
    - 87-2172 | Balkind (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-564)
    - 87-2172 | Backind (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 87-2173 | Cummings (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 87-2174 | Pratt (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 87-2175 | Cornelius (Jalbert) (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 87-2176 | Noah Finkel L. H. (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 87-2176 | Finkel (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-545)
    - [87]-2177 | Trevor Sr. (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 87-2179 | Whitman Village (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 87-2180 | Berry (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 87-2181 | Rosen (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-550)
    - 87-2182 | Burrwood (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 87-2182 | Burrwood Orig. Blueprints for 1916 Addition (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 87-2182 | Burrwood (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 87-2182 | Burrwood (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 87-2182-C | Burrwood (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 87-2182-C | Burrwood (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 87-2182-C | Burrwood (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 87-2183 | Nissoquogue Golf Club (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 87-2183 | Nissequogue Golf Club (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 87-2183 | Nissequogue Golf Club (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 87-2184 | Burbeck Res. Fairfield (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 88-2185 | Barrow (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 88-2185 | Barrow (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 88-2188 | Henderson (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 88-2188 | Henderson (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 88-2192 | Pittella (2 rolls) (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 88-2192 | Pittella Res. | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - 88-2200 | Seminary of the Immaculate Conception (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 88-2201 | Burr Residence Matinicus Island Maine (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 88-2203 | Donovan (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 8[8]-2205 | Bergman Res. Alts. and Add. (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 88-2206 | Miller (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 88-2209 | Arthur (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 88-2215 | Hershey (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 88-[unknown job number] | Tobias Add. to Res. (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 89-229 | Weidel (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-564)
    - 89-2211 | Burton - Addition to Res. (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 89-2216 | Kuhnel (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 89-2217 | Stamm (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 89-2221 | Orofino (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 89-2223 | Jacobs (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 89-2224 | Silver (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 89-2232 | Oak Tree Farm Dairy (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 89-[unknown job number] | CSH Firehouse Record Prints - Graeser (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-545)
    - 89-[unknown job number] | Goodwin Aug. 22, 1989 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 89-[unknown job number] | [Fahaures] Sept. 6, '89 [New (illegible notes) "Blue Ridge"] (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 89-[unknown job number] | Fiveson 7-14-89 (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 90-2235 | Trevor, Jr. Garden Trellis (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 92-2238 | Donaldson (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 92-2247 | Murray (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 92-[unknown job number] | E. V. Post Jr. (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 93-2249 | Riggs (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - [illegible]-[1676] | [Mylar Negatives] Hill School negative of mylar (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-541)
    - [unknown job number] | Mission House 3rd, 4th, 5th W. 46th, NYC (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - [unknown job number] | [Lloyd Harbor] [unknown, found loose in box, unlabeled] (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - [unknown job number] | Burrwood (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - [unknown job number / misc. job number] | Post Estates Surveys (misc.) (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - [unknown job number] | C. S. H. High School (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-581)
    - [Various Job Numbers] | [Various Jobs] | [labels from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)